http://www.vanik.com/vanik_privacy_policy

Ask An Expert
×
Coming Soon!!
#Guaranteed Response Or Money Back Vanik - Largest Online-To-Offline Platform On Distribution Trade
USEFUL LINKS
About Us Services Why Vanik Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Contact Us
PRIVACY POLICY
Vanik (Vanik) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.Vanik.com.
Our site uses forms to allow users to sign up for free membership, The registration form requires users to give us email address. This information is used to correctly address emails to registered subscribers.
Vanik.com offers free trial membership for limited usage of Vanik resources. Free trial members may upgrade to paid membership and gain full access to all resources available at Vanik.com. The registration form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address, tel, fax email address etc). This information is used to gather demographic information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company, special trade alerts, free ezines and occassionally promotional material. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the customer when necessary.
Vanik.com uses a Paid Membership Form for customers to enlist as paid member. This information is used to interact with members, sending special trade alerts, e-Zines, trade communications etc. The Membership fee is paid through bank check/draft etc. We use a secure payment gateway operated by one of the most reputed banks in India for collecting credit card payment. The credit card information is handled by the bank directly through its secure payment gateway. We/our server never collect Credit Card information.
Vanik.com site allows its visitors to post (free of cost) messages for business community. The inquiry forms require users to give us contact information (like your name, address, tel, fax email address etc). This information is used to gather demographic information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company, free e-zine and occassionally promotional material. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the customer when necessary.
None of this collected information will be provided to third parties, except in the case of a requirement by law enforcement. In such case, the requested information will be provided to appropriate government authorities upon receipt of necessary documentation. Vanik.com follows a rigorous anti-spam policy - including never to send unsolicited email, always masking email addresses to stop spamming, not to disclose email information in private or public display etc.
This site contains links to many other sites. www.Vanik.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice, particularly how to opt out of advertising cookie or to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here
Public Forums This site makes use of forms (including response forms) and bulletin boards to allow users to post distribution related offers. Personal information (such as email address, phone number) is collected in these forms to allow registered users such as manufacturers, importers, distribution partners etc, to contact concerned members posting message. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We do not monitor any of these facilities and your use of them is at your own risk.
Choice/Opt-Out Vanik.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database or not to receive future communications or to no longer receive our service:
On-line removal Every Special Alert, e-zine that we send has a link for immediate and on-line 'Unsubscribe'. Subscribers may remove themselves from any of our mailing lists by clicking at 'Unsubscribe' link. Every trade alert, e-zine has clear instructions on how to 'Unsubscribe'
Permanent Removal/Termination of Membership Any member (free or paid) can terminate his/her membership of Vanik.com by log-in to MyVanik Dashboard and de-activate his/her registration. This process automatically removes the member's profile from directory listing amd mailing lists. Alternatively any user may request us to terminate his/her membership/registration at any time. Such de-activated members never receive any e-mail from us except reply e-mail in case he/she has written to us. However, we do not monitor public forums and bulletin boards. In case such de-activated member has posted any message in a public forum, he/she needs to inform us for removal of such message giving specific URL
Opt-out via email Additionally. one may send e-mail at mail@Vanik.com for unsubscription/opt-out or contact us
Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact
Customer Service
Vanik (Vanik.com)
Ace InfoBanc Pvt Ltd
124 - A/1, Shaheed Jeet Singh Marg
Katwaria Sarai,
New Delhi - 110 016
India
Mobile : +91 9210373801
Tel: 91-11-26961886 / 26866235 / 26851944
E-Mail: mail@Vanik.com
SIGN IN
User Name
Password
Remember Password
Forgot Password ?
New Visitor : Please Sign Up
REQUESTACALL
Please Fill This Form
*Select Your Role
I am / We are Manufacturer Importer Trader Retailer / Retail Chain Distributor Dealer Stockist Agent Service Provider Propaganda cum Distributor(PCD) 3rd Party manufacturer C&F Agent Super Stockist Newcomer Others
Your Name
Company
Email ID
Phone / Mobile
City / State
Country
Message
7 - 5 = ?
Submit
Please rotate your device We don't support landscape mode yet. Please download APP or go back to portrait mode for the best experience
